Guide to the Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, 1865-1950
Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, 1865-1950
- M
  - Master, Arthur, M. "Low-voltage t waves in the electrocardiogram." Reprinted from the American Journal of Medical Sciences, February 1931. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Meningococcemia with Endocarditis." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Medical Association, 17 January 1931. (Box 3)
  - ________ and A. Romanoff. "Electrocardiographic changes in pneumonia." Reprinted from Proceedings of the Society of Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1930. (Box 3)
  - May, Charles. "Method in Medical Study." Reprinted from The New York Medical Journal, 18 September 1886 (Box 3)
  - Mayo, N. S. "Cattle Poinsoning by Nitrate of Potash." Experiment Station of the Kansas State Agricultural College, Bulletin No. 49, May 1895. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Texas itch." Experiment Station of the Kansas State Agricultural College, No. 69, June 1897. (Box 3)
  - Mazer, Charles and A.J. Ziserman. "The present status of female sex hormone therapy." Reprinted from Medical Journal and Record, 6 January 1932. (Box 3)
  - McAlister, Harold. "Dairy breed comparisons VII: official butter records of breeds." Holstein-Friesian Association of America pamphlet, 1917. (Box 3)
  - McCaw, Walter D. "Walter Reed, a memoir." Walter Reed Memorial Association, 1904. (Box 3)
  - McBryde, C.N. "The germicidal value of liquor cresolis compositus (u.s.p.)." U.S. Department of Agriculture Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 100, 31 May 1907. (Box 3)
  - McClintock, Charles T. "A new, practical disinfecting material." Reprinted from the Medical News, April 1897. (Box 3)
  - McCord, Clinton P. "Physical and mental condition of delinquent boys." Reprinted from Albany Medical Annals, April 1919. (Box 3)
  - McCulloch, Charles. "The teeth of the horse as affected by age, part I." Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 116, September 1900. (Box 3)
  - __________. "The teeth of the horse as affected by age, part II." Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 116, September 1900. (Box 3)
  - ________. "The teeth of the horse as affected by age, part III." Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 116, September 1900. (Box 3)
  - ________. "The teeth of cattle and sheep as affected by age." Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 118, November 1900. (Box 3)
  - ________. "The most common irregularities of the teeth of the horse, part I." Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 119, December 1900. (Box 3)
  - ________. "The most common irregularities of the teeth of the horse, part II." Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 119, January 1901. (Box 3)
  - McEachern, Donald. "A study of the morbid anatomy of hearts from patients dying with hyperthyroidism." Reprinted from Bulletin of the Johns Hopkins Hospital, May 1931. (Box 3)
  - McEachran, Duncan. "Veterinary sanitary science: a brief historical sketch of early history of live stock quarantine in Canada." Dominion of Canada Department of Agriculture (Box 3)
  - McFarland, Joseph and Edward M. L'Engle. "Observations upon the phagocytic power of the blood of supposedly normal human beings." Reprinted from Medicine, April 1906. (Box 3)
  - McGrew, T.F. "American Breeds of Fowls: I-The Plymouth Rock." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, 1901. (Box 3)
  - ________. "American Breeds of Fowls: II-The Wyandotte." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, 1901. (Box 3)
  - McInerney, T.J. and H.C. Troy. "A comparative study of some methods for determining the fat content of skim milk." Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No 401, January 1920. (Box 3)
  - McWhorter, V.O. "The sheep-killing dog." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin, 16 April 1915. (Box 3)
  - Meleney, Frank L. "Infections of skin and the subcutaneous tissue." Bulletin of the New York Academy of Medicine, October 1930. (Box 3)
  - Melvin, A.D. "Report of the chief of the bureau of animal industry." U.S. Department of Agriculture annual report, 22 December 1906. (Box 3)
  - Mendel, Gregor. "Experiments in plant-hybridisation." Read at the meetings of the 8th February and 8th March, 1865, of the Royal Horticultural Society of London. (Box 3)
  - Menyhert, S. "Allatbiztositas." VIII. Nemzetkozi Allatorvosi Kongresszus Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Mercer, William Fairchild. "The development of the wings in the lepidoptera." Reprinted from Journal of New York Entomological Society, March 1900. (Box 3)
  - Merck. "Penicillin." n.d. (Box 3)
  - Metler, Fred A. and Leonard Goss. "The brain of the giant panda." Reprinted from the Journal of Comparative Neurology, February 1946. (Box 3)
  - Metzger, H.J., F.E. Hull and Fordyce Ely. "Albuminuria and nephritis in dairy cows." Kentucky Agricultural Experiment Station, University of Kentucky, Bulletin No.373, July 1937. (Box 3)
  - Metzger, H.J. and W.A. Hagan. "The so-called stiff limbs." Reprinted from the Conrell Veterianrian, January 1927. (Box 3)
  - Milks, H.J. "Convulsions in dogs." Reprinted from the 1926 Annual Report of the State Veterinary College. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Diseases of the cornea." Reprinted from the Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, December 1922. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Disease of the perineum." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian Vol.XX, No.2, April 1930. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Disease of the perineum." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College, 1929-1930. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Experiments with bacterium anthracis, anthrax vaccines and hyperimmunization." Agricultural Experiment Station of the Louisiana State University and A. and M. College, Louisiana Bulletin No.109, August 1908. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Hog cholera and anti-hog cholera serum." Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College, Cornell University. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Intussusception in dogs." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, April 1924. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Persistance of the right instead of the left primitive aorta in the dog, incarcerating the esophagus and causing its dilation." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, October 1935. (Box 3)
  - ________. "A preliminary report on some diseases of chickens." Agricultural Experiment Station of the Louisiana State University and A. and M. College, Louisiana Bulletin No.108, August 1908. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Primary brain tumors in small animals." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, April 1936, Vol.XXVI, No.2. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Skin diseases in small animals." Reprinted from Lederle Veterinary Bulletin, Vol.III, No.5, September-October 1934. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Some diseases of the abdomen." Reprinted from the Report of the New York State Veterinary College for the year 1930-1931. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Some diseases of the genito-urinary system." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXIX, April 1939, No.2. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Some of the more recent remedies." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University for the year 1928-1929. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Tumors of small animals." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXII, No.2, April 1932. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Uses of some drugs acting upon the circulatory system." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXIII, No.2, April 1933. (Box 3)
  - Miller, Malcolm E and Ralph E. Witter. "Applied anatomy of the external ear of the dog." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, January 1942. (Box 3)
  - Miller, Richard C. "Stomach worms in sheep." University of Kentucky, College of Agriculture, Extension Division, Circular No.152, February 1936. (Box 3)
  - Minett, F.C. "Bovine mastitis." Eleventh International Veterinary Congress, London, 1930. (Box 3)
  - (Box 3)
  - Minot, Charles Sedgwick. "Gegen das gonotom." Reprinted from Anatomischer Anzeiger, ca. 1893. (Box 3)
  - ________. "The embroyological basis of pathology." Reprinted from the Boston Medical and Surgical Journal, 28 March 1901. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Structural plan of the human brain." Reprinted from Popular Science Monthly, July 1893. (Box 3)
  - ________, et al. "The relation of the American Society of Naturalists to other scientific socities." Reprinted from Science, 21 February 1902. (Box 3)
  - Mohler, John R. "Infectiveness of milk of cows which have reacted to the tuberculin test." United States Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 44, 1903. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Milk fever: its simple and successful treatment." U.S.Department of Agriculture Farmers' Bulletin No. 206, 1904. (Box 3)
  - ________. "The tuberculin test of cattle for tuberculosis." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin No. 351, 1909. (Box 3)
  - ________and Geo. Byron Morse. "Necrotic stomatitis with special references to its occurrence in calves (calf diphtheria) and pigs (sore mouth)." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 67, 1905. (Box 3)
  - ________ and Henry J. Washburn. "Foot-rot of sheep its nature, cause and treatment." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bulletin No. 63, 1904. (Box 3)
  - ________and Henry J. Washburn. "Takosis, a contagious disease of goats: a preliminary report on its nature, cause and prevention." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 45, 1903. (Box 3)
  - ________ and Henry J Washburn. "Tuberculosis of hogs." United States Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulleti, No. 781, February 1917. (Box 3)
  - Moller, J.D. and Wedel I Holstein. "Description of a remarkable, beautiful and complete collection of type slides of diatoms mounted between the years 1886-1890. "1890. (Box 3)
  - Moore, Veranus A. Actinomycosis Mistaken for Tuberculosis at Post-Mortem Following the Tuberculin Test. American Veterinary Review, May 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. Address of the President [at AVMA meeting, New Orleans, 17 Nov 1919]. Journal of American Veterinary Medical Association, December 1919. (Box 3)
  - ________ w/ Walter J. Taylor. Agglutination Method of Diagnosis in the Control of Glanders. Journal of Infectious Diseases, 1907. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ Walter J. Taylor and Ward Giltner. Agglutination Method for the Diagnosis of Glanders [read at AVMA meeting, New Haven, September 1906]. American Veterinary Review, October 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. American Veterinary Education and its Problems [read at AVMA meeting, Toronto, August 1911]. Science, 13 October 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______. Ammoniacal Fermentation of Urine [proceedings of the American Society of Microscopists]. American Monthly Microscopial Journal, June 1891. (Box 3)
  - _______. Animal Experimentation: The Protection it Affords to Animals Themselves and its Value to the Live-Stock Industry of the Country. Defense of Research Pamplet VI, Issued by the Council on Defense of Medical Research of the American Medical Association, 1909. (Box 3)
  - _______. Apartment Incubator for Student Use [read at the American Microscopial Society meeting, Columbus, August 1899]. Journal of Applied Microscopy, ca.1899. (Box 3)
  - _______. Apparatus for Holding Cover Glasses. Proceedings of the American Society of Microscopists, 1891. (Box 3)
  - _______. Attempt to Eradicate Bovine Tuberculosis from Cattaraugus County. Veterinary Medicine, July 1929. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ Archibald R. Ward. Avian Tuberculosis. Proceedings of AVMA, 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bacillus Coli Communis. Medicine, March 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bacteria in Milk: A Summary of the Present Knowledge Concerning their Source and Significance, NYS Dept of Agriculture pamphlet, 1902. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bacteriology in General Education [ read at Society of American Bacteriologists meeting, Ithaca, 28 December 1910]. Science, 24 February 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ H.A. Harding and George A. Smith. Bang Method of Controlling Tuberculosis, with an Illustration of its Application. NYS Agricultural Experiment Station Bulletin, April 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. Blackhead, or Infectious Entero-Hepatitis, In Turkeys [Bureau of Animal Industry Circular no 5 (1896), revised]. US Dept of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Circular, 2 December 1905. (Box 3)
  - _______. Blood Serum in the Prevention and Treatment of Infectious Swine Diseases with a Report of an Experiment with Swine Plague Antitoxin. Proceedings of Society for the Promotion of Agricultural Science, Detroit, August 1897. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis. Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station of the College of Agriculture Bulletin, February1905. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis. Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station of the College of Agriculture Bulletin, January 1908. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis [same as "Bovine Tuberculosis: Its Diagnosis and Control"]. Transactions of the Chicago Pathological Society, 1 April 1918. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis Control. Proceedings of the World's Dairy Congress, 1923. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis: Its Diagnosis and Control [read at the joint meeting of the Chicago Pathological Society and the Chicago Medical Society, 6 February1918]. Bulletin of the Chicago Medical Society, ca. 1918. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis and Methods for its Control [Proceedings of the Association of American Agricultural Colleges and Experiment Stations]. US Dept of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations Bulletin, 1909. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis: Its Problem and Control. American Veterinary Review, January 1912. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis in its Relation to Man [7 March 1927]. De Lamar Lectures, 1926-1927. (Box 3)
  - _______. Bovine Tuberculosis in New York State. Report for the Joint Committee of the Committee on the Prevention of Tuberculosis of the NY Charity Organization Society and the Milk Committee of the NY Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor, 7 October 1907. (Box 3)
  - _______. Can Tuberculosis be Eliminated from Cattle? New York State Journal of Medicine, May 1908. (Box 3)
  - _______. Causes for Tubercle Bacilli in Market Milk and Methods for the Control of Bovine Tuberculosis. American Veterinary Review, June 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______. Chairman's Address: Laboratory Section, American Public Health Association, Havana, Cuba. Annual Report of American Public Health Association, n.d. (Box 3)
  - _______. Character of the Flagella on the Bacillis Cholerae Suis (Salmon and Smith) Bacillus Coli Communis (Escherich) and the Bacillus Typhi Abdominalis (Eberth). Wilder Quarter-Century Book, 1893. (Box 3)
  - _______. Character of the Flagella on the Bacillis Cholerae Suis (Salmon and Smith) Bacillus Coli Communis (Escherich) and the Bacillus Typhi Abdominalis (Eberth). Proceedings of the American Microscopial Society, 1895. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ Clarence M. Harding and Bert J. Cady. Clinical Examination of the Blood of the Horse and its Value to the Veterinarian. Proceedings of the AVMA, 1904. (Box 3)
  - _______. Contribution to the Study of the Myelin Degeneration of the Pulmonary Alveola Epithelium. Proceedings of the American Microscopial Society, 1893. (Box 3)
  - _______. Control of Bovine Tuberculosis. Read at the NY State Dairymen's Association Meeting, Elmira, December 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. Control of Bovine Tuberculosis: Report of the International Commission of the AVMA, Sept. 1910. US Dept of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Circular, 17 March 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______. Control of Bovine Tuberculosis. Read at International Association of Milk Dealers meeting, Detroit, October 1926. (Box 3)
  - _______. Control of Bovine Tuberculosis, n.d. (Box 3)
  - _______. Control of Diptheria in Small Cities and Country Districts from the Bacteriological Standpoint [read at New York State Medical Association meeting, New York, October 1900]. New York State Medical Journal, February 1901. (Box 3)
  - _______. Control and Prevention of Bovine Tuberculosis in Individual Herds [part of AVMA Committee on Diseases report, Philadelphia, September 1908]. American Veterinary Review, October 1908. (Box 3)
  - _______. Cornell's Contribution to Veterinary Medicine. Cornellian Council Bulletin, March 1925. (Box 3)
  - _______. Diagnosis of Rabies: It's Spread and Methods of Control in New York. Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College, 1908-1909. (Box 3)
  - _______. Direct Transmission of Infections Entero-Hepatitis in Turkeys. US Dept of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Circular, 1896. (Box 3)
  - _______. Diseases of Animals Communicable to Man. American Journal of Public Health, February 1927. (Box 3)
  - _______. Dissemination and Control of Tuberculosis as Illustrated in the Bovine Species. Proceedings of Conference of Sanitary Officers, NY State Department of Health, 1907. (Box 3)
  - _______. Duncan McEachran and the McGill Faculty of Comparative Medicine. Journal of the AVMA, February 1922. (Box 3)
  - _______. Education and Veterinary Medicine. Journal of the AVMA, Nov 1926. (Box 3)
  - _______. Elimination of Tubercle Bacilli from Infected Cattle and the Control of Bovine Tuberculosis and Infected Milk. Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station of the College of Agriculture Bulletin, May 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______. Elimination of Tubercle Bacilli from Infected Cattle. Journal of Medical Research, June 1911. (Box 3)
  - _______. Etiology and Prevention of Infectious Diseases of Animals [read at Veterinary Medical Society of New Jersey meeting, Trenton, 8 January 1903]. American Veterinary Review, February 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______. Exercises Attending the Presentation of the Portrait of Dr. James Law by the Alumni of the New York State Veterinary Collage to Cornell University, 14 May 1909. (Box 3)
  - _______. Factors Involved in Tuberculosis Eradication and in Maintaining Sound Herds [read at Eastern States Conference on Tuberculosis, June 1924]. Cornell Veterinarian, July 1924. (Box 3)
  - _______. Foot and Mouth Disease and its Eradication. Read at Foot and Mouth Disease Conference, Chicago, November 1915. (Box 3)
  - _______. Foot and Mouth Disease in Illinois. Read before the Illinois General Assembly, 19 January 1915. (Box 3)
  - _______. Foot and Mouth Disease: What It Is, What It Does, How to Fight It, and How to Prevent It: Every Farmer's Duty in This Crisis. Doubleday, Page and Co., 1914. (Box 3)
  - _______. Fowl Plague: A New Chicken Disease, in America. Cornell Veterinarian, January 1925. (Box 3)
  - _______. Fundamentals in Free Masonry. Read at the Dedication of the Masonic Temple, Ithaca, 2 October 1926. (Box 3)
  - _______. Growth of Veterinary Science and the Application of New Knowledge [read at Conference for Veterinarians, New York State Veterinary College, 14 January 1926. Cornell Veterinarian, April 1926. (Box 3)
  - _______. Healthy Herd from a Tuberculous Herd. New York Agricultural Experiment Station Bulletin, April 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. Hemopast: A New and Convenient Instrument for Drawing Blood for Microscopic Examination. American Microscopial Society, 1897. (Box 3)
  - _______. How the New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University is Meeting the Veterinary Needs of the State and Country [presented at Cornell University Trustee meeting, 10 Nov 1917].Proceedings of the Board of Trustees of Cornell University, 10 November 1917. (Box 3)
  - _______. Incubator for Student Use. (Box 3)
  - _______. Inefficiency of Milk Separators in Removing Bacteria. Yearbook of the US Dept of Agriculture, 1895. (Box 3)
  - _______ w/ Theobald Smith. Infectious Diseases Among Poultry. US. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Bulletin, 1895. (Box 3)
  - _______. Influence of Animal Experimentation upon Agriculture [read at Society for the Promotion of Agricultural Science meeting, Buffalo, August 1896]. Proceedings of the Society for the Promotion of Agricultural Science, 1896. (Box 3)
  - _______. Inquiry Concerning the Source of Gas and Taint Producing Bacteria in Cheese Curd. Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station of the College of Agriculture Bulletin, January 1899. (Box 3)
  - _______. Inquiry into the Alleged Relation Existing Between the Burrill Disease of Corn and the so-called Corn-Stalk Disease of Cattle. Agricultural Science, 1894? (Box 3)
  - _______. Limitations of Tuberculin in Detecting Tuberculosis Infected Animals. New York State Veterinary College Annual Report, 1914-1915. (Box 3)
  - _______. "Mastitis" and "Bang Abortion Diseaseand Undulant Fever" [in The Production and Handling of Milk As it Affects Public Health]. New York State Department of Health, n.d. (Box 3)
  - _______. Meat Inspection. Read at Conference of Sanitary Officers of the State of New York, 1906. (Box 3)
  - _______. Method for Tabulating the Description of Species Bacteria, ca. 1903. (Box 3)
  - _______ with F.L. Kilborne, E.C. Schroeder, Theobald Smith and C.W. Stiles. Miscellaneous Investigations Concerning Infectious and Parasitic Diseases of Domesticated Animals. US. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Bulletin, 1893. (Box 3)
  - _______. Morbid Anatomy and Etiology of Avian Tuberculosis. Journal of Medical Research, 1904. (Box 3)
  - _______. Mouse Septicaemia Bacilli in a Pig's Spleen, with some Observations on their Pathogenic Properties. Journal of Comparative Medicine and Veterinary Archives, 1892. (Box 3)
  - _______. Nature and Diagnosis of Rabies and its Extent in New York. New York State Department of Agriculture, 1909? (Box 3)
  - _______. Nature and Prevention of Infectious Enter-Hepatitis in Turkeys. Cultivator and Country Gentleman, 25 March 1897. (Box 3)
  - _______. Nature of Foot and Mouth Disease. Cornell Veterinarian, February 1915. (Box 3)
  - _______.Natural in Disease [ read at American Microscopial Society Meeting, Syracuse, Aug-Sep 1898]. Transactions of the American Microscopial Society, May 1899. (Box 3)
  - _______. Nodular Teniasis in Fowls. US. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Circular, 1895? (Box 3)
  - _______. Non-Motile Pathogenic Bacillus Closely Resembling the Bacillus of Hog Cholera Found in the Lung and the Spleen of a Pig - see Miscellaneous Investigations Concerning Infectious and Parasitic Diseases of Domesticated Animals. (Box 3)
  - _______. Normal Bacterial Invasion of the Cow's Udder. Proceedings of the Twentieth Annual Meeting of the Society for the Promotion of Agricultural Science, 1899. (Box 3)
  - _______. New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University. Science, 2 January 1914. (Box 3)
  - _______. Observations Concerning the Significance of Streptococci in Comparative Pathology. American Veterinary Review, Jan Feb Mar 1900. (Box 3)
  - _______. Observations on Bacillus Coli Communis from Certain Species of Domesticated Animals. American Medicine, 29 March 1902. (Box 3)
  - _______. Observations on the Morphology, Biology and Pathogenic Properties of Twenty-Eight Streptococci Found in the Investigations of Animal Diseases. Proceedings of the American Microscopial Society, June 1894. (Box 3)
  - _______. Observations on Staining the Flagella on Motile Bacteria. Proceedings of the American Microscopial Society, 1891. (Box 3)
  - _______. On the Flagella of Motile Bacteria. Proceedings of the American Microscopial Society, 1896. (Box 3)
  - _______. Opening Remarks [read at Annual Conference for Veterinarians, Ithaca, 1929]. Cornell Veterinarian, 2 April 1929. (Box 3)
  - _______. Outbreak of Rabbit Septicaemia. American Veterinary Review, September 1893. (Box 3)
  - _______. Outlook for Veterinarians. Cornell Veterinarian, April 1925. (Box 3)